Published using Google Docs

Chive Media Group - Privacy Policy - Revised 12-11-2019

Updated automatically every 5 minutes

Chive Media Group, LLC

Privacy Policy

The following Privacy Policy covers all of the websites of Chive Media Group, LLC, Resignation Holdings, LLC and all subsidiaries and affiliates (collectively, “Chive Media Group”, “we” or “us”), as well as the Mobile Services (as defined below) or desktop application services, software, or other materials or services made available on, from, or through Chive Media Group’s websites (collectively, the “Websites”). This policy does not, however, apply to entities that Chive Media Group does not own or control, such as applications and websites using Facebook Platform. If you create a Chive Media Group account using Facebook or another third-party social media service, or if you link your Chive Media Group account with any of these third-party services, we may share your information with these third-party services. This Privacy Policy applies only to information collected by the Websites.

Please read this policy. If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us.

By using the Websites, you understand and agree that Chive Media Group is providing a platform for you to post content, photos, comments and other materials (collectively, “User Submissions”) to the Websites and to share User Submissions publicly. This means that other users may search for, see, use, or share any of your User Submissions that you make publicly available through the Websites, consistent with the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy and Chive Media Group’s Terms of Use.

Collection and Use of Aggregated Information

Chive Media Group creates aggregate reports on user demographics and traffic patterns. These aggregated statistics are used internally to better provide services to users of the Websites. They may also be provided to advertisers, sponsors, and partners; however, they contain no individual personal information and cannot be used to gather such information. This allows Chive Media Group’s advertisers, partners, and sponsors to advertise more effectively, as well as allows our users to receive advertisements that are pertinent to their needs.

Ownership of Information

Chive Media Group is the sole owner of the information collected on the Websites. This includes:  

(i)         Your username, password and email address when you register for an account on a Website.

(ii)        Profile information that you provide for your user profile (e.g., first and last name, picture, phone number). This information allows Chive Media Group to help others find your profile on the Websites.

(iii)        User Submissions that you post to the Website.

(iv)        Communications between you and Chive Media Group. 

Chive Media Group may offer certain services that are available via a mobile device or app, including (1) the ability to upload User Submissions to the Websites via a mobile device, (2) the ability to browse the Websites from a mobile device and (3) the ability to access certain features through an application downloaded and installed on a mobile device (collectively, “Mobile Services”). If you use Mobile Services, Chive Media Group may store information regarding your mobile device, including your device type and operating system, the advertising ID of your mobile device, location services (if you grant permission), or in other applications as permitted by the functionality of such mobile device.

In addition, Chive Media Group may access, collect, monitor, store on your device, and/or remotely store one or more “device identifiers.” Device identifiers are small data files or similar data structures stored on or associated with your mobile device that uniquely identify it. A device identifier may be data stored in connection with the device hardware, data stored in connection with the device’s operating system or other software, or data sent to the device by Chive Media Group. A device identifier may deliver information to Chive Media Group or to a third-party partner about how a user browses the Websites and may help Chive Media Group or a partner provide user reports, personalized content or targeted ads. Some features of the Websites may not function properly if use or availability of device identifiers is impaired or disabled.

How We Use Your Information

Chive Media Group uses the information you provide, or that we collect, to provide services and features to you; to operate, maintain, and enhance its Websites; to provide users with customer support; as well as to track user-generated content and users to comply as a service provider with the Digital Millennium Copyright Act (“DMCA”) and other applicable laws. Chive Media Group also uses information to prevent potentially illegal activities. These efforts may, on occasion, result in a temporary or permanent suspension or termination of some functions for some users.

Chive Media Group may also contact you with announcements related to the Websites from time to time. You may opt out of all communications, except essential updates on your account.

Chive Media Group does not share your information with advertisers without your consent. Chive Media Group allows advertisers to choose the characteristics of users who will see their advertisements and Chive Media Group may use any of the non-personally identifiable attributes it has collected (including information you may have decided not to show to other users, such as your birth year or other sensitive personal information or preferences) to select the appropriate audience for those advertisements.

Even though Chive Media Group does not share your information with advertisers without your consent, when you click on or otherwise interact with an advertisement, there is a possibility the advertiser may place a cookie in your browser or the advertising ID for the Mobile Services and note that it meets the criteria they selected.

Chive Media Group may share User Submissions and your information (including but not limited to, information from cookies, log files, device identifiers, location data, and usage data) with businesses that are legally part of the same group of companies that Chive Media Group is part of, or that become part of that group (“Affiliates”). Affiliates may use this information to help provide, understand, and improve the Websites and Affiliates’ own services; however, these Affiliates will honor the choices you make about who can and cannot see your photos.

In addition to other information described in this policy, we may collect and share precise location information, through methods such as mobile “SDKs”. This location information may be used by itself, aggregated, or combined with mobile identifiers (such as IDFAs and Android IDs), and shared with third parties, for purposes related to advertising, attribution (e.g., measuring ad performance) analytics and research. You can remove your consent to having your location data collected by changing the settings on your device. (Certain services may lose functionality as a result.) You can opt-out from any interest-based advertising through your device settings. When you have opted out using this setting on a device, advertisers will not use in-app information collected from that device to infer your interests or serve ads to that device that are targeted based on your inferred interests.

Content and Metadata

The Websites are intended to share text, graphics, photos, sounds, music, videos, audiovisual combinations, and other materials (collectively “Content”) you may view on, access through, or contribute to the Websites.  If you do not want us to store metadata associated with the Content you share on the Websites, please remove the metadata before uploading the Content.

Exclusions

This Privacy Policy does not apply to any information collected by Chive Media Group other than information collected through the Websites and shall not apply to any unsolicited information you provide to Chive Media Group through the Websites or through any other means. This includes, but is not limited to, Content or other information posted to any public areas of the Websites, such as comments, any ideas for new products or modifications to existing products, and other unsolicited submissions (collectively, “Unsolicited Information”). All Unsolicited Information shall be deemed to be non-confidential and Chive Media Group shall be free to reproduce, use, disclose, distribute and exploit such Unsolicited Information without limitation or attribution.

Comments 

In order to enhance their use of the Websites, users can choose to post comments on particular articles of interest. Chive Media Group does not endorse these comments, as they are opinions of users not associated with Chive Media Group or its employees.

Mailing List 

Chive Media Group may launch an email mailing list for some or all of its Websites. In order to receive regular emails, newsletters and the like from a mailing list from one of the Websites, users must submit information including, without limitation, a valid email address and demographic information. This information will be used in anonymous, aggregate form only in order to assess general user interest in various internal and third-party products and services. Your personal contact information will not be passed to any other organization. Users who choose to sign up for a mailing list will receive regular emails from the site, including new articles added to the site as well as, from time to time, emails from third-party site sponsors. If you do not wish to receive emails from third-party advertisers, do not sign up for the mailing list.

Public Forums 

The Websites make chat rooms and message boards available to its users. Any information disclosed in these areas becomes public information. Please exercise caution when deciding to disclose your such information.

Cookies 

Some of Chive Media Group’s business partners may use cookies on the Websites or advertising IDs for the Mobile Services (collectively, “Cookies”). However, Chive Media Group has no access to or control over these Cookies; this Privacy Policy covers the use of Cookies by Chive Media Group only and does not cover the use of Cookies by any advertisers.

In addition, the Websites use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”).  Google Analytics and Chive Media Group’s business partners use Cookies to help analyze how users use the Websites. The information generated by the Cookie about your use of the Websites will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google and Chive Media Group’s business partners will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the Websites, compiling reports on activity for operators and providing other services relating to internet usage.  Google and Chive Media Group’s business partners may also transfer this information to third parties when required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google’s or Chive Media Group’s business partners’ behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google.

You may refuse the use of Cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your internet browser, or by enabling the Do Not Track settings in your browser. Please note, if you do this, you may not have full access to the Websites.  By using the Websites, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google and Chive Media Group’s business partners in the manner and for the purposes set out above.

Third Party Advertising 

The ads appearing on Websites are delivered to users by third-party advertisers including Google, among others. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.  If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click here. We use third-party companies to serve ads and collect non-personally identifiable information when you visit our Websites. These companies often use a Cookie or third-party web beacons to collect information. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here:  [https://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/](https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/&sa=D&source=editors&ust=1733969455795372&usg=AOvVaw1jXQy5541DcmVakPYAgqt2).  Additionally, Chive Media Group’s sites participate in the Digital Advertising Alliance’s (DAA) Self-Regulatory Program for Online Behavioral Advertising within advertising units that link to [http://www.aboutads.info/choices/](https://www.google.com/url?q=http://www.aboutads.info/choices/&sa=D&source=editors&ust=1733969455795907&usg=AOvVaw2oWsXLmPfR3NfjdthtgPCe).

Log Files

Like most standard website servers, we use log files. This includes internet protocol addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. We may use a tracking utility that uses log files to analyze user movement. This information is not linked to personally identifiable information.

Legal Disclosures

Chive Media Group may need to disclose personal information when required to do so by law or legal process.  Chive Media Group may also share information when it has a good-faith belief that such action is necessary:

(i)        to comply with a current judicial proceeding;

(ii)        to obey a court order or legal process served on any of the Websites;

(iii)        to prevent fraud or other illegal activity;

(iv)        to prevent imminent bodily harm; or

(v)        to protect Chive Media Group and users from people violating these Terms.

Business Transitions

In the event Chive Media Group goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of a portion of its assets, or if Chive Media Group declares bankruptcy, Chive Media Group may transfer the aforementioned collected information as part of the assets transferred.

Links

The Websites contain links to other sites. Please be aware that Chive Media Group does not control and is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of other sites. We encourage users to be aware when they leave our Websites and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Chive Media Group.

Notification of Changes

Whenever Chive Media Group changes its Privacy Policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, and other places deemed appropriate.

Violations of this Policy

Chive Media Group may terminate your access to its Websites, if, under appropriate circumstances, Chive Media Group determines you violated this Privacy Policy.

Other Data Protection Rights

In the event you are located in certain countries that fall under the scope of the European General Data Protection Regulation (aka, the “GDPR”), data protection laws give you rights with respect to your personal data, subject to any exemptions provided by the law, including the rights to:

●      Request access to your personal data;

●      Request correction or deletion of your personal data;

●      Object to our use and processing of your personal data;

●      Request that we limit our use and processing of your personal data; and

●      Request portability of your personal data.

You may reach us at [privacy@thechive.com](mailto:privacy@chivemediagroup.com) to exercise any of these rights. We may reject requests that are unreasonable or not required by law, including those that would be extremely impractical, would require disproportionate technical effort, or could expose us to operational risks.  Please note, that by deleting your data, your ability to access the service may be disrupted.

Controllers and Responsible Companies.  Chive Media Group is controller (or co-controller) of all customer personal information, which means that Chive Media Group is the company that determines the purposes for which, and the way in which, personally identifiable information is processed, and is responsible for processing that information, based on the particular service being provided to you. Depending on the services, more than one company may be the controller of your personal data.

California Privacy Rights

The California Consumer Privacy Act provides some California residents with the additional rights listed below:

Right to Know. You have the right to know and see what data we have collected about you over the past 12 months, including:

* The categories of personal information we have collected about you;
* The categories of sources from which the personal information is collected;
* The business or commercial purpose for collecting your personal information;
* The categories of third parties with whom we have shared your personal information; and
* The specific pieces of personal information we have collected about you.

Right to Delete. You have the right to request that we delete the personal information we have collected from you (and direct our service providers to do the same). There are a number of exceptions, however, that include, but are not limited to, when the information is necessary for us or a third party to do any of the following:

* Complete any transaction(s);
* Provide you a good or service;
* Perform a contract between us and you;
* Protect your security and prosecute those responsible for breaching it;
* Fix our system in the case of a bug;
* Protect the free speech rights of you or other users;
* Comply with the California Electronic Communications Privacy Act (Cal. Penal Code § 1546 et seq.);
* Engage in public or peer-reviewed scientific, historical, or statistical research in the public interests that adheres to all other applicable ethics and privacy laws;
* Comply with a legal obligation; or
* Make other internal and lawful uses of the information that are compatible with the context in which you provided it.

Right to Opt-Out / [Do Not Use My Info](mailto:privacy@thechive.com). You may request that we no longer use your personal information for the aforementioned purposes. To do so, you may contact us at [privacy@thechive.com](mailto:privacy@thechive.com).

Exercising Your California Privacy Rights. To request access to or deletion of your personal information, or to exercise any other data rights under California law, please contact us at [privacy@thechive.com](mailto:privacy@chivemediagroup.com).

How Should a User Contact Chive Media Group LLC?

If you suspect that Chive Media Group has handled your information in a manner that does not comply with this Privacy Policy, or if you wish to exercise any of your aforementioned rights, please contact us at [privacy@thechive.com](mailto:privacy@thechive.com).

Updated: December 11, 2019
